{
    "subject": "resource/DuraCloud",
    "predicate": "ontology/programmingLanguage",
    "object": "resource/Java_(programming_language)",
    "human_readable": "DuraCloud is written in Java.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9257434010505676,
            "question": "Is DuraCloud primarily developed using Java?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8415114879608154,
            "question": "What programming language is DuraCloud written in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7821175456047058,
            "question": "Could DuraCloud potentially be rewritten in a different programming language?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7808541059494019,
            "question": "Are there any performance implications associated with using Java for DuraCloud?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7113147377967834,
            "question": "Is there a large community of developers who specialize in Java and could contribute to DuraCloud's development?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6360554099082947,
            "question": "What are the potential benefits of using Java for DuraCloud's development?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6357335448265076,
            "question": "Can we assume DuraCloud's codebase relies on Java libraries and frameworks?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6270478963851929,
            "question": "Would a Java developer find it easier to understand DuraCloud's source code?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5960779786109924,
            "question": "How does the choice of Java for DuraCloud's development align with its intended purpose and functionality?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.286493182182312,
            "question": "What other software projects are commonly written in Java?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=DuraCloud is written in Java.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8592_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How does the choice of Java for DuraCloud's development align with its intended purpose and functionality?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8592_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Would a Java developer find it easier to understand DuraCloud's source code?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8592_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can we assume DuraCloud's codebase relies on Java libraries and frameworks?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8592_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8592_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8592_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8592_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8592_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8592_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8592_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8592_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8592_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8592_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8592_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nThe provided text mentions that DuraCloud has REST-based code libraries for Java, PHP and Python, meaning developers can use these languages to interact with it. It doesn't explicitly state that DuraCloud itself is written in Java. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The provided context does not contain any specific information about the programming language used to write DuraCloud. While it mentions a command-line Java application for uploading content, this does not necessarily imply that DuraCloud itself is written in Java. Therefore, based on the given information, we cannot confirm that DuraCloud is written in Java."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "While the provided text mentions a command-line Java application used with DuraCloud, it doesn't explicitly state that the entire DuraCloud application itself is written in Java.  It focuses more on the availability of Java libraries for integration and the open-source nature of the project under the Apache 2.0 license.",
            "category": -1
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "It was mentioned that a command-line Java application was provided to upload content into a DuraCloud instance, but the application itself wasn't demonstrated during the preconference session, implying that it's not directly related to the DuraCloud service.",
            "category": -1
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information does not specify the programming language used to develop DuraCloud. While a command-line Java application for uploading content was mentioned, this does not imply that DuraCloud itself is written in Java. It could be developed using other languages and frameworks, with Java being one of the tools utilized for certain functionalities or integrations.",
            "category": -1
        }
    }
}